appeargame.com 2013-07-31

# PRIVACY POLICY

PRIVACY POLICY

The privacy of our visitors to AppearGame.com is important to us.

At AppearGame.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit AppearGame.com, and how we safeguard your information.  We never sell your personal information to third parties.

**What We Collect**

We may collect the following information:

  *  Name and last name

  *  contact information including email address

  *  demographic information such as Contry, preferences and interests

  *  other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

**What We Do With The Information We Gather**

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping.

  * Names and email are not going to be published. Any other information will appear on each user's profile page.

  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.

  * We may periodically send promotional email about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.  

  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. 

  * We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.

**Security**  
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Athough we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

**Disclosure of your Information**   
 We may disclose your personal information to third parties:

  * If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our Terms and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of AppearGame.com, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

  * Where we receive a complaint from a third party that any contribution made by you is defamatory, or infringes their copyright or other intellectual property rights and we are requested to disclose your personal data (address, proper name, and telephone number) to them to enable them to make contact with you direct in order to pursue their complaint.  It shall not be necessary for us to verify truthfulness of the complaint before we disclose this information, but we will endeavour to notify you of the complaint as soon as reasonably practicable.

  * If The Redhammer Management Limited or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets.

**Log Files**  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files.  The information in the log files include  your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site.  This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

We also use third party advertisements on AppearGame.com to support our site.  Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed.  This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

**DoubleClick DART cookies**  
We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements).  This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (”interest based targeting”).  The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey).  DART uses “non personally identifiable information”.  It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers.  You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting [ http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx)  

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security.  However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites.  This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program.  Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

**Children Under Age 13**

AppearGame.com does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, you're not allowed to create an account in this site.
